<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="com_google_android_gms_fonts_certs">com_google_android_gms_fonts_certs
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="level_1">
        <item>Emphesize Problem Solving</item>
        <item>Level #1</item>
        <item>A manual or help system should help users solve problems in the workplace. Some problems might include:
        "How can I organize this project?" "Where should company invest development time?" or "Where can I find the peak intensity of data?"
        You can help the user through introductory paragraphs that preview not only the steps to follow, but the goals and objectives of their
        software work, "Writing to Teach, you have opportunities to encourage creative solutions</item>

        <item>Example on Emphasize problem solving strategy:
                                   TaskOrientedStrategies application helps the student that takes documentation course
                                   to learn the nine strategies of how to develop task-oriented document in easy and fun way.</item>

        <item>What are the problems that face user in workplace when using manual?</item>
        <item>How to develop new project?</item>
        <item>How can i organize this project?</item>
        <item>First + Second.</item>
        <item>None of the above.</item>

        <item>When using manual or help system that includes problem solving, How it help the users?</item>
        <item>solve problems in workplace, preview not only steps to follow but objectives and goals.</item>
        <item>Make easy report to the project admin.</item>
        <item>None of the above.</item>
        <item>First + Second.</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="level_2">
        <item>Provide Task-Oriented Organization</item>
        <item>Level #2</item>
        <item>Organize a manual or help system in a way that matches the kinds of tasks a user will perform. or example a word processing
            manual that follows the "open a file type in words, save the file exit the program" sequence would seemmore logical than one
            organized alphabetieally for example, or according to the menus of the program. A task-oriented arrangement begins in the table
            of contents (of your manual) or the introductory screen (of your help system). As the following chapters will show,
            a task orientation should pervade the design of your manual or help system so that even the seemingly mechanical forms of reference
            have the right touch to make them very functional in the workplace.</item>

        <item>Example on Task-Oriented Organization strategy:
        in TaskOrientedStrategies application first you have to press start button to transfer you to the game level,
        then you start learning throw level to getting more pro in this game until you finish the nine levels and last
        but not least you can view your total effort after finishing them.</item>

        <item>What Task-Oriented organization means ?</item>
        <item>means organize the manual in regular way.</item>
        <item>organize in way that matches the kinds of tasks a user will perform.</item>
        <item>First + Second.</item>
        <item>None of the above.</item>

        <item>How to organize manual in task-oriented manner?</item>
        <item>Based on alphabetical order or what user like to perform first.</item>
        <item>Based on sequance of actions and logical organization.</item>
        <item>None of the above.</item>
        <item>First + Second.</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="level_3">
        <item>Encorage User Control Of Information.</item>
        <item>Level #3</item>
        <item>Encourage "User control of information' means the feeling, among software users, that they decide what the program does
            for them To encourage this the manual should users how to make key decisions, supply key information, or determine key
            program outputs Examples include: specifying what a database program will search for and identifying which data the program
            will process . Users need to feel in control of the program.
            Cross-references in manuals and hypertext links in online systems can help maintain the user's
            sense of control over the documentation because these document design elements allow users to choose where they go for additional
            information, or where to proceed after they have finished a section.
        </item>
        <item>Example on Encourage User Control Of Information strategy:
              Specifying what a database program will search for and identifying which data the program
        will process.</item>
        <item>How to make the user manual encourage users control of the information?</item>
        <item>Show the user steps how to follow and control the layout of the information.</item>
        <item>Teach the user how to make key decisions, supply key information, determine key program output.</item>
        <item>First + Second.</item>
        <item>None of the above.</item>

        <item>How Corss-reference and hypertext links in online system help user to control over the documentation?</item>
        <item>Allow the users to balance graphics and text and also to maintain the appropriate density of print.</item>
        <item>Make the document easy to use or maintain information.</item>
        <item>None of the above.</item>
        <item>First + Second.</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="level_4">
        <item>Orient Pages Semantically</item>
        <item>Level #4</item>
        <item>Semantic orientation in page design means you arrange the elements of the page meaningfully, according to elements of the
            job the user needs to perform. Other examples of semantic organization include putting important elements first and making important
            elements larger to help users apply the program to their work. One of the best way to orient pages semantically employs visuals
            and graphics to balance text in a complementary way. "Laying Out Pages and Screens discusses ways to balance graphics
            and text and also to maintain the appropriate den sity of print and legibility of letters. These basic elements can contribute
            to the usability information in the workplace.
</item>
        <item>Example on Orient Pages Semantically strategy:
                                   Organize the tasks based on the flow of events or scinario that the user needs to perform
        and putting importanat elements first, making them in larger fonts.</item>

        <item>What Semantic Orientation design means?</item>
        <item>Design the document in alphabatical order</item>
        <item>Desgin the document based on how the user want see it.</item>
        <item>Based on putting important elements first and make it in larger fonts.</item>
        <item>None of the above.</item>

        <item>How to orient pages semantically?</item>
        <item>Make all the details explicit to the user.</item>
        <item>Employs visuals and graphics to balance text in a complementary way.</item>
        <item>None of the above.</item>
        <item>Third + Second.</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="level_5">
        <item>Facilitate Routine and complex tasks.</item>
        <item>Level #5</item>
        <item>As Barbara Mirel points out, users of software face both routine tasks and complex tasks. Routine tasks include
            repeatable tasks that are easily represented by convtional procedures. She points out, however, that
            "Complex tasks differ from routine tasks such as data entry of standard accounting calculations because they are not performed
            the same way every time. Routine tasks are often those represented by menu functions in a program
            ("Save a file "Delete a record and so on) but complex tasks require the user to apply knowledge that isn't easily
            codified in step-by-step procedures. This knowledge, called tacit or pragmatic knowledge consists of insider knowledge
            that comes from years of experience. Using a spreadsheet to schedule employees fairly, or using a word processor to
            identify trends in annual reports: these tasks are highly dependent on the situation surrounding the user and can not
            be easily represented by manuals that cover only menu functions However, the more you can help users apply software to
            complex tasks the more users will value your manual or help system. You learn about users' routine and complex tasks
            during the user analysis, "Analyzing Your Users.</item>

        <item>Example on Facilitate Rotine and complex tasks strategy:
                                   Rotine Tasks such as: tasks in word processor (save file, delete record and open file)\n
                                   Complex Tasks such as: tasks that needs experience and pragmatic knowledge such as (calculate the average salary
                                   in excel and install windows OS in device).</item>

        <item>What Complex Tasks means?</item>
        <item>Tasks that requires experts and profisonals to perform.</item>
        <item>require the user to apply knowledge that isn't easily
            codified in step-by-step procedures</item>
        <item>First + Second.</item>
        <item>None of the above.</item>

        <item>What is the difference between routine and complex tasks?</item>
        <item>Routine Tasks is more complex to perform.</item>
        <item>data entry of standard accounting calculations because they are not performed
            the same way every time.</item>
        <item>None of the above.</item>
        <item>First + Second.</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="level_6">
        <item>Design For Users</item>
        <item>Level #6</item>
        <item>Design for Users (user-driven) The concept of user-driven design means that the organization of a manual comes from the
            user\'s needs rather than from models or templates what a user's Hook -or from schemes based on giving some users one kind
            of information and other users other information. According to Janice Redish, user-driven design should allow users to
            Find what they need, Understand what they find and Use what they understand appropriately User-driven design requires the kind
            of extensive user analysis "Conducting Usability Tests." It
            means that each manual or help system presents you with new design challenges that you can only meet by involving the
            user in the document development process ,you will find that each of the topic areas discussed in that chapter ties
            in to specific techniques, such
            as using icons to suggest key points or tables to show how features and their uses can add to the task orientation,
            and thus the value, your documents.
</item>
        <item>Example on Design For Users strategy:
                                   Such as the interactive manual first time it popup tells the users
            first task to do and it designed to match the user\'s needs.</item>

        <item>What User-Driven means?</item>
        <item>means that the organization of a manual comes from the
            user\'s needs rather than from models or templates</item>
        <item>Let the user control what details popup for him/her</item>
        <item>First + Second.</item>
        <item>None of the above.</item>

        <item>What User-Driven allows to users?</item>
        <item>desgin the document based on how the user like to.</item>
        <item>Find What they need, understand what they find and apply what they understand.</item>
        <item>None of the above.</item>
        <item>First + Second.</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="level_7">
        <item>Facilitate Communication Tasks</item>
        <item>Level #7</item>
        <item>Users of software programs work in contexts that require them to communicate about their work. These tasks are called
            communication tasks because they depend on the user's workplace demands rather than on a narrow view of program features.
            Face it just opening a file is only part of the picture from the user's perspective-the user opens a file so that he or
            she can communicate information to another person, not for its own sake. Document designers can help users see the why
            behind the program fea tures by analyzing what kinds of information users need and how they communicate and then identifying
            those program features for example, print functions, report functions, or disk output functions-that support communication tasks.
            Also, communication tasks are facilitated by tasks that transfer data from one application to another How do you help users
            with communication tasks? Learning about the user's communication tasks presents a great opportunity to record the common
            terminology for procedures and tasks—the "jargon" that you can use and writing steps and explanations.
</item>
        <item>Example on Facilitate Communication Tasks strategy:
                                   Every action that the user communicate with the document(how to get specific information,
                                    how to retrive data and what information i need to know).</item>

        <item>Why when the users communicate with the software for workplace called communication tasks?</item>
        <item>they depend on the user's workplace demands rather than on a narrow view of program features.</item>
        <item>Because they communicate with the project admin.</item>
        <item>Because they communicate with the project clients.</item>
        <item>None of the above.</item>

        <item>One of these examples on Facilitate Communication Tasks is correct?</item>
        <item>Interview clients, support ideas to project and feedback from users.</item>
        <item>print functions, report functions, or disk output functions.</item>
        <item>Specify the what type of information i need to get from this app.</item>
        <item>None of the above.</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="level_8">
        <item>Encourage User Communities</item>
        <item>Level #8</item>
        <item>Users often need encouragement to rely on other users of the program, their user community; task-oriented documentation
            encourages users to identify and get help from others. Other users of the program, while not exactly experts in the software,
            can render valuable help because they understand the user's job demands. Companies foster user communities with mailing lists,
            article archives, and contact lists other information specifically for users of their products. Figure 1.4 shows an ex ple user
            community web page for users of a popular media playing program. a person writing, say, a for this program, this site would
            provide valuable information about the users of the product. User communities,
            "Analyzing Your Users provide a wealth of information about user tasks. Users can also help support y evelopment effort.
             "Planning and Writing Your Documents discu the of including users in the development process through interviews
            and cl idea can help provide candidates for this kind of user involement reviews. User communities document development.

</item>
        <item>Example on Encourage User Communities strategy:
                                   go to these websites to get to get more information about this topic Such as dell support system,
            Windows media technology and stackoverflow.</item>

        <item>What we mean by user communities?</item>
        <item>Your colleagues at work?</item>
        <item>Other users of the program that have job demands and expirence</item>
        <item>First + Second.</item>
        <item>None of the above.</item>

        <item>How user communities helps user in their workplace?</item>
        <item>Encourage user to rely on other users to get valuable information.</item>
        <item>To get better solutions for problems in user workplace.</item>
        <item>None of the above.</item>
        <item>First + Second.</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="level_9">
        <item>Support Cognitive Schema</item>
        <item>Level #9</item>
        <item>Since the advent of computerized work in business and industry, we have learned much about how users process information.
            We have learned that people use mental models, called cognitive schema, that help them learn new information,
            process the information, and apply the information that comes at them at an alarmingly faster and faster rate.
            The task-oriented manual uses principles of knowledge representation, parallelism, and analogy to convey software
            features and applications to workplace tasks. "Writing to Support-Reference,
            allow users to absorb what your manual or help system has to say with as little effort as possible For the modern professional
            in business and industry, the software program lies at the heart of the knowledge management problem because computers both
            represent the cause and the solution to the problem. Computers generate comple information, and computer software allows
            the user to store, transfer, and present Our it. understanding of how computers affect work grows through research on the
            impact the point of on people's work and workplace roles. If we explore software use from good view of the user's information
            environment, we sce a strong need for software documentation.
</item>
        <item>Example on Support Cognitive Schema strategy:
                                   TaskOrientedStrategies application helps the student that takes documentation course
                                   to learn the nine strategies of how to develop task-oriented document in easy and fun way.</item>
        <item>What is the Cognitive Schema?</item>
        <item>a set of steps the user perform to get help from others.</item>
        <item>is a mental model help users to process information.</item>
        <item>First + Second.</item>
        <item>None of the above.</item>

        <item>How users get help from Cognitive Schema?</item>
        <item>Ask other communities.</item>
        <item>learn new inforamtion, process the information and apply the information.</item>
        <item>None of the above.</item>
        <item>First + Second.</item>

    </string-array>

</resources>